seogdk.com 2018-03-07

# Privacy Policy | SEO Expert : Seogdk

This  _Privacy Policy_  governs the manner in which Seogdk collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://www.seogdk.com](http://www.bloggingcage.com/) site (“Website”). This  _privacy policy_  applies to the Website and all products and services offered by Seogdk.

###  **Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our website, register on the website, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Website. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website-related activities.

###  **Non-personal Identification Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Website. The non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Website, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Our Website may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly.

###  **How We Use Collected Information**

Seogdk collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:  

  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Website.

  * _\- To improve our Website_  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

###  **How We Protect Your Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Website.

###  **Sharing Your Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Website and other websites on the Internet. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

###  **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Seogdk has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Website, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

###  **Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use our Website. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at:  
  
**Gangadhar Kulkarni**  
**Admin  
Pune, Maharashtra**

**India  
+919011538001**

**seogdkulkarni@gmail.com/admin@seogdk.com**

This document was last updated on Jan 09, 2018

**\-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------**  
******\-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------****
